Frost fills the sky over
Ten Mile Lake
Silken threads anxicus of
youth.
Looking at the moon and
feeling lonely.
Envious of love, not of
imortality.
This pointing will remind
you of me.
Sian's grave?!
Sian died long ago.
She's ghost?!
Yes! l'm a ghost but l bring
mortals no harm.
l died far away from my home
An evil spirit took by corpse and
won't let me rest in peace.
lf you want to save me, move
my bones away from here.
Then it will be possible for
me tobe reincarnated.
Sian!
l will save you.
Ning!
Let them go, please.
The Diamond Sutra!
We've escaped!
Sian, we're safe!
Dawn is breaking.
Sian, hide in the tower of ashes.
lf the sun's rays shine on
you, you'll never be reincarnated.
Ning, good-bye forever!
l hope that Sian will be reincarnated.
l must return to the Orchid
Buddhist Monastery.
lf you need me, you can find
me there. Take care!
Looking for the way,
the way of freedom.
Sea and mountains,
l have traversed countless times.
A thousand paths,
all leading to my homeland.
The endless verdent mountains,
The mountains everywhere,
in howling wind and driving rain.
The path of the ancient garden.
Why does it never end?
The way of the Tao, the way of freedom.
Devils and demons always
pronounce themselves good.
The anger of youth
Weeping ghosts and angry spritis,
Times gone-by,
Why was there such a sea of blood?
The path of the ancient garden
Why can one never return on it?
Who is that young man?
He's the poor schoolar who
lived 2 blocks away.
Things have changed since he
was last here.
Wasn't he that shop's bill
collector?
He doesn't even know it went
out of business long ago!
Welcome! Welcome!
The bill collector's here.
How much money did you collect?
We're here to catch escaped convicts.
lt's the police! Run!
Pursue them!
You're Bing Chow?!
You've made a mistake.
He has a beard and l don't!
You shaved it off!
Take him back and collect the reward.
Get in!
l haven't committed any crime!
Let me got. l've been
wrongly accused!
Let me got l've been
You're made a mistake.
l'm not Bing Chow!
l am wrongly accused!
My name is Ning,
not Bing Chow.
Old man may l ask who...
A man just like you,
fated to being imprisoned.
So pessimistic!
lt's all my elders' fault,
insisting l get an education
When l grew up, l was
learned and wrote books.
But when l write of my travels,
l'm accused of revealting state secrets.
When l write of history,
they say l'm satirizing the present.
lf l analyse milltary strategy,
they say l'm planning arebellion.
l can't even write fairy tales, for they
accuse me of promoting superstition.
Finally, l wrote the
biography of a powerful man.
Then he was arrested,
accused of being a rebel.
We here both sentenced to
life imprisonment.
Wouldn't you say that prison
is my fate?
A cockroach!
Where?
Cockroach?!
You're really wasteful! The
cockroaches here are of the best quality.
There are no delicacies here
After you're been here a while,
you'll even salivate ever a housefly.
Old man, how long have you
been here?
l was your age when
l first arrived.
Look how l've changed!
Full of character!
You've been here a long time
Help! l am innocent!
l'm not Bing Chow!
l am innocent!
You've made a mistake.
l'm not Bing Chow!
Another nightmate.
What did you dream this time?
l dreamt you were haggard
and exhausted.
Exhausted?! True, you will
soon be totally exhausted.
You have nightmares every night.
Look at the calendar.
You've been here so long and
still can't adjust.
Soon you'll even forget that
your last name is Chow.
Old man, my last name
isn't Chow!
Bing Chow!
Supper!
OK.
A chicken leg?!
Happy days are here again!
Old man! There's only one
bowl. You eat first.
No, it's for you. l'd rather
eat cockroaches.
l'll tell you something when
you've finished.
l haven't had chicken in
a long time.
Old man, why are you carving
my name?
All these men ate chicken legs.
We call that chicken a
headless chicken.
After you've eaten it, they
chop off your head!
Chop off your head?!
Bing Chow, we have no
personel quarrel.
Don't come back from the
greve and seek revenge on me
They behead people at noon.
lt's now the middle of the night.
Some official's son got in trouble,
and they're looking for a substitute.
At night, the executioner
can't tell one from another.
ls there no justice in the world?
ls there no reward
for being a good man?
lt is of no concern to me.
l was always an honest man.
l'll give you whatever l can
This painting was a gift
from my dearest one.
l don't want to part with it
even in death.
Young man, you have a good heart.
Let me give you a present.
You are so learned.
lt is fortunate that l die
rather than you.
You're a good man.
Such a pity you have to die.
lt would be a pity if you
died, not me.
Anybody's death is a pity.
You're a rare speciman.
lf you die, your type will be extinct.
lt's been a long time since
l set somebody free.
This tunnel leads to the outside.
Go out and start a new.
Don't give me such false hopes.
lf this is an escape route,
why didn't you escape long ago?
lt's less troublesome for me
to write my book here.
When l finish, then l'll
escape and get it printed.
Don't worry about me.
Always keep this bundle
with you.
Once you're out of here,
never come back!
Get going!
What will happen to you
after l've gone?
They like hearing my stories
So long as l don't get to
the story's end,
they'll never harm me.
But they'll accuse you of
helping me escape.
l'll say you were put to
death for somebody else 2 days ago.
They won't dare make a fuse.
Go!
Take care!
Bing Chow! The time has come
Bing Chow!
He's dead.
l've escaped!
There's even a horse here
waiting for me!
That old man is really remarkable!
l must repay his kindness someday.
Hey! That's my horse!
What a stupid horse!
Letting a stranger ride him!
l don't even have time
to wash my hands!
You think you're fast over land...
l'll go underground!
Open sesame!
l must find a place to get
out of this downpour!
Good! A house!
Open the door!
''Righteous Villa''...
Anybody home?
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8
8 coffins! Must be the
whole family.
l won't disturb you.
l just want to stay the night.
Don't bother to get up.
l'll take care of myself.
l told you not to go any
trouble. Please go back!
The way you rush about in no
fixed direction!
l had a hard time following
you underground.
Don't you have any idea
where you're going?
Your face looks so horrible,
you must have suffered a painful death.
lf you'd rushed around
underground all day like me,
you wouldn't have the energy
to come back to the surface.
l don't know you. Why are
you following me?
l don't know you either, so
why did you take my horse?
That's your horse?
l thought it was the
old man's.
Still you should have asked
before taking it.
You're alive! Sorry! lt's
all a misunderstanding.
lf there's anything l can do
to help, just let me know.
Enough of your tricks!
A good thing my reactions are so fast.
Friend, you need a place to
stay the night.
Here there's a roof over your head.
Might as well stay here.
How do l know what you'd
do after l fell asleep?
l knew it!
Let's draw up some boundaries.
l'm staying next door.
lf you have something to say
shout it! Don't come over.
l haven't bathed in a long time.
The way
The spoken ''way'' is not ''way''
Of haven and earth,
Of humang and swards
Of evil and good,
This way, that way, every which way
Say that their way,
is the only way
Bah. Tehah, hah!
All bullshit,
This way, that way,
is still not the way
Ha! Ha!
The way of flowers and tea, Ha!
Of life and death,
Of density and intensity,
Of light and heat,
Of evil spirits
Of people committing crimes
Of bed ones in power! Ha!
l find my own way
l seek
My way!
Who is it?
Are you a mortal?
Hey, friend next door! Get
up! There's ghosts!
Get up! Do you hear me?
Hurry and get up!
Not a sound. Maybe he left already.
What a nuisance!
Friend, there are fierce ghosts here!
Ghosts? l'll use my maglo to
banish them!
Ghosts and goblins,
l order you to leave!
Oh, you understand the occult!
My nose is sensitive to
other worldly spirits...
So why do l smell nothing now?
Get out of the way!
Abracadabra!
Strange! Not even a hint of
ghostly odour!
Abracadabra! Hocus-pocus
flash!
Abracadabra!
Don't come here!
Leave!
You're not even real ghosts!
Wasting my occult talents.
Phonies?
Want to trick me?
A good thing you have a
waistband.
Stay away from me!
l'm falling...
Stop hugging me!
Let go!
lf l let go, l'll fall!
lf you don't let go, l'll...
Sian?!
Sian!
Hocus-pocus heebie-jeebie!
l order you to freeze!
Freeze!
Sian, is that you?
What kind of black magic is
that? Let them go!
Otherwise l'll kill him.
Oh...Freeze!
Kill him! He's no friend of mine!
Elder Chu! Are you Elder Chu,
travelling incognito?
Elder who?
Your disciple is deeply sorry.
Disciple?!
Elder Chu?!
Sian, it's me! Don't you
recognize me?
We come from a good family.
My name is Windy.
This is my younger sister,
Moon.
Elder Chu.
Elder, you can save us.
My father is Lord Fu, the
ex-Minister of Rites.
He was framed. They're now
transporting him to be executed.
We want to attack the
transport wagon and rescue him.
You are the learned and
brilliant Chu.
You two are loyal imperial warriors.
Everyone is an eminent personnage.
Now it's my turn to
introduce myself,
l am...Spell!
My name is Autumn,
from the Kunlun sact.
l've read everything that
the Elder has written.
l only use my magic to battle demons.
l never get involved in
affairs of state.
We pay our respects to Elder Chu.
My name is Ning, not Chu.
l can tell you are clever.
Clever people do not always
reveal their identities.
Anyway, in our hearts we
know who you really are.
How can l make you believe
me?
No need for you to say
anything. Everybody remember
From now on, Elder Chu will
be known as Ning.
Chu is Ning.
Yes!
We will now take an oath.
Whoever reveal their identities will be
chopped up into 10,000 pieces.
Yes!
Such an honour that you rode
my horse!
Sian, do you remember this
painting and poem?
Sian? Poem?
He's reciting poetry.
Quickly, pen and paper.
We must record what he says.
Elder is giving us a hint.
Hurry!
Frost fills the sky over 10
Mile Lake;
Silken threads anxious of youth.
Looking at the moon and
feeling lonely;
Envious of lovers, not of
immortality.
Very profound!
What does ''10 mile'' mean?
10 mile!
lt is all very deep.
His words are too profound!
10 Mile? That must mean 10
Mile Pavilion.
There's a 10 Mile Pavilion
near hear.
That's right! Sister, ''10 miles''
refers to 10 Mile Pavilion.
lt's nearby.
l understand. 10 Mile Pavilion
is not far from here.
''Frost'' refers to Frost's
Descent.
Each year has 24 climatic
periods...
After the autumnal equinox
comes the frost...
and today is the day of
Frost's Descent.
Elder is telling us that father will be
transported past 10 Mile Pavilion.
He's telling us to rescue him there.
Elder is truly perceptive.
We can save father.
We had it right!
Good.
lt hurts!
What's the matter? Get up!
Reporting!
Miss Windy! Your father will pass
the 10 Mile Pavilion tonight.
We already know that.
Elder is truly brilliant!
But what about the rest of the poem?
What do those 2 stanzas mean
3 stanzas.
The meaning doesn't matter now.
lnterpret it in any way you desire.
He means that we should have
our own views...
not just listen to what
other people say, right?
So, should we still listen
to what Elder says?
Not only listen, but take
notes and ponder his meaning
We must pass his wisdom on
to future generations.
Right!
Time to leave!
Good-bye.
We're off to 10 Mile
Pavilion.
Yes. We're off to 10 Mile
Miss Windy, please return
Sian's painting to me.
Yes, Elder.
When you call me Sian, is
that a hint that l need a pseudonym?
From now on, my name is Sian
lf Sian were reincarnated,
she would now be a babe in arms.
She's not Sian!
What are you spying on?
Me?...Nothing.
l wanted to see what you
were spying on. Time to go!
Do you think your fiance,
Prince Ma...
is as handsome as Elder?
We were betrothed before birth.
How do l know what he looks like?
ls that what people mean by fate?
Who are you referring to?
Oh, nobody. lt's just that l
feel so fortunate.
Fortunate? You're frothing
at the mouth!
Evil spirits!
ls this a foot print or a hand print?
We'll know when we find the
monster.
Right!
lt even harmad a man.
What a pity to leave it here
Better show it to Elder.
OK! There really are ghosts
in this place!
What is that?
A corpse! lt's all that
ghost's fault.
Don't hug it. Put it down.
How did this person die so
pitifully?
l'd say this an evil ghost.
The odour is very strong.
lt's back!
ls it looking for us?
Use your ''freeze'' magic.
Right!
l command you to freeze!
Heebie-jeebie! Freeze!
That'll stop him!
How do you do it?
When you see a ghost, shout ''freeze''.
Like this? Freeze! ls that right?
Oh, no! How do you lift the spell?
l have to think of a way to
communicate with him.
What can l do? Let's try
this...
lf l'm right, move your eyes
up and down.
That's right! Fantastic!
lf l'm wrong, move them from
left to right.
Great!
Will a hand gesture lift
the spell?
What? Not up and down or
left to right.
Don't joke with me.
lf we wait too long, that
monster will get us.
Does lifting the spell have
to do with an acupuncture point?
Your eyes are moving faster
than a revolving lantern!
l understand! You're
provoking me into hitting you.
OK. l'm going to hit you now
Ready or not, here it comes!
Let's get out of here!
Come on!
You're too heavy. l can't carry you.
Drag it! Dragging you isn't fast
enough either.
Better hide upstairs.
l told you not to fool
around at a time like this.
That monster is so tall,
it'll see us if he stand up straight.
How can l undo the spell?
lt's safer inside. Better
hide yourself quick.
l told you to hide inside.
Why did you go down there,
where it's so dangerous?
Try the ''freeze'' curse!
Freeze!
Let's continue with out
guessing game.
You're getting heavier and
heavier. Can't carry you much longer.
Since that monster isn't here...
let's try to lift the spell.
Does it have anything to do
with this amulet?
Yes?! What then?
Point at me. Point at me and
the curse will be lifted.
Point!
How do l undo the spell?
Freeze!
Don't move!... Move! Move!
Don't move!
Why does he ''unfreeze'' so quickly,
but you haven't moved for so long?
Do you mean...l pointed to
this amulet...
Then l asked you how to lift
the spell...
And he moved! Freeze!
l'll take care of it.
Get out of here fast!
Finally lifted the spell!
Get out of here!
Abracadabra! Open up a way out!
Out of the way! l'll take care of it!
Abracadabra!
Hocus pocus!
l order all ghosts to be expelled!
Wow! lt doesn't fear my
incantations!
lt's still moving!
l order all ghosts to be
expelled!
Even when it's chopped up he
can still run away!
lt could still come back at
any time.
Elder, get out of here.
l'll pursue it!
Be careful!
Earth, open up!
Hey! Stop! Stop!
Are you stupid? l told you to stop!
We don't even know each other.
Why are we fighting?
l learned magic to deal with
evil spirits.
lf you don't stop, l'll use
my magic to ''freeze'' you.
Why are you blocking my way?
l was just taking a rest
after battling some ghosts,
and you say l'm blocking
your way.
When that monster makes a run for it
tonight, you'll be in deep trouble.
Brother!
Call me Master.
Master, your skill is extraordinary.
lf you worked for the imperial court,
your future would be boundless.
You know that l'm a
Taoist monk.
Seeking wealth and position
is for the likes of you mere mortals.
l don't want to end up like
you...Earth, open up!
What a pity.
Hu, our horses' hoofs are
rigid. They won't move!
lt must be that monk's
magic at work!
He said there are evil
spirits. Be careful!
Yes!
Lord Fu!
There's nothing l can do
about squabbles in the imperial court.
lt's hard to tell right from wrong.
l'm just following orders.
But don't worry.
l'll make sure your journey is safe.
After we get to the capital,
whatever the emperor does to
you is not my responsibility
Let's go!
Where can l get something to eat?
Please give me a bowl of
your cheapest food.
What? The cheapest?
Sit down! lf you're starving
don't waste your money.
Show me your face.
Go!
Stand up.
Don't lower your head.
Go!
Don't run away!
Don't move!
Monks?
Stand still!
Out of the way!
Get out of the way!
What kind of magic is this?
lt's Windy...
Come back!
Hey!
The soldiers never come to
10 Mile Pavilion last night.
Rush back to Righteous Villa
and lie in ambush for them.
Hey!
Back to Righteous Villa?
lt's haunted!
Come back!
Elder! Elder!
l wonder if Elder has
already gone?
Better search for him.
Yes!
Do you think father's
transport has already passed by here?
No. They're not supposed to
reach here until after dark.
Miss Windy, the villa has
been ransacked.
l'm sure Elder did it to
remove any traces of our presence.
Set everything up. Prepare
to attack.
Yes!
Hurry up! Over there!
Who is it?
l'm Ning.
Ning?
Oh, it's Elder!
This villa is haunted.
Haunted?
Where is Miss Windy?
lnside.
Ghosts?
Real ghosts?
Miss Windy!
My clothes!
Elder, they said you came.
Miss Moon!
Who are you?
Oh, it's Elder. l recognize
your back.
Elder...
l...
With your beard shaved off,
you're so, so...
Yes.
When my sister sees you,
she'll be so happy for me.
Happy?!
When you came in, did you
see my sister?
Your sister? No. No!
Sister! Sister! Sister!
What are you grinning about?
lt is improper to look.
There are some things you
shouldn't look at.
You're all right!
l didn't recognize Elder
with his beard shaved off.
Really? l must see for
myself.
Elder, if you have something
to say, just say it.
lt scares me when you hint
at things.
l'm cold.
Your face is so hot, how
can you be cold?
Wouldn't this be faster?
Not fast enough. Faster
would be better.
Faster?!... OK.
Elder...
Elder said he was cold.
Cold?
Elder, you're overly
exerting yourself.
Have you seen Miss Windy?
No, l'm looking for her too.
Where did she go?
There's noise coming from upstairs.
Let's go up for a look.
Don't go up there.
Strange! Nobody up here.
Maybe it's next door.
Let's go over and look.
What are you doing?
Sister, Elder came back to
find me...us.
Why are your clothes so
dishevelled?
Don't be so impolite in
the future.
Miss Windy, this villa is
haunted.
Do we still have to pretend
to be ghosts?
No matter what, we must wait
here for father.
We mustn't leave.
ln this moment of danger,
we must thrust out our
chests and be fearless.
We must be utterly devoted
to our cause.
Elder, let's go in.
Elder!
Your clothes are
torn in the back.
How do you write the
''freeze'' incantation?
l didn't spy on him.l didn't
even know he was outside.
Better tie your heart down.
Otherwise, it might fly away
lf l could tie it down, l would!
This is how you do it...
lt works!
This is the ''freeze''
incantation.
lf you see that monster, do
this and he'll freeze in his tracks.
Like this?
Don't do it haphazardly.This
spell is hard to reverse.
Give me your hand.
Yes!
Sister, what's that sound?
lt's coming from up there.
Windy!
Windy, give me your hand.
Elder, shouldn't you be
calling me Sian?
Whether l call you Sian or
Windy, there's no need to be bashful.
l'll never reveal what
happened just now.
l was really anxious on
your behalf.
Actually, l kissed you
because l couldn't control myself.
Fortunately you made a
quick get-away.
Otherwise, if Moon had seen
you undressed and with me...
it would be hard to explain,
even if l were Elder Chu.
Give me your hand.
Moon?!
Moon, what are you doing here?
l was looking for you.
Don't bother explaining.
Moon!
No, Windy! Give me your hand
We're not fated for each other.
l'm betrothed to Lord Ma's son.
You're betrothed?
We weren't meant for each other.
You should be looking for
Moon, not me.
Windy, one at a time. l'm
after both of you.
Miss Moon, it's getting dark
Give me your hand.
Go to my sister instead.
l'll go to her next. Quick,
give me your hand.
Elder, aren't you the playboy!
You can only choose one of us.
l'm not going to compete
with my sister.
No need to compete. When l
finish with you l'll go to her.
Elder, there is something
l must tell you.
Actually, love is a strange thing.
My heart beats wildly when
l look at you.
l don't even have the
courage to glance at you.
l'm afraid that my heart
would jump right out.
Help!
What's that?
Hurry up! That monster is back.
Go inside and search.
Yes!
lnside there's a huge creature.
l don't know what it is.
Be calm! Use the ''freeze''
incantation.
Together : Freeze!
lt sure does!
We froze it in its tracks.
Everybody, jump up there!
The archery machine!
Be careful!
Elder!
Moon, go and rescue Elder.
l'll lure away that monster.
Yes!
Put out the net.
Your hand...
Let's retreat from here.
See what's going on up ahead
Yes!
Soldiers!
Hu, they've set up an ambush
Windy, Moon?!
lt's father!
Lure the soldiers into the villa.
Use the archery machine to
mow them down!
Trying to get away?
The monster destroyed the
archery machine!
We're surrounded by our toes
Let me out!
Right!... Let Elder go!
Elder, what should we do now?
We'll stay on the sidelines.
When the enemy comes in, the
monster will deal with them.
Obviously a fake ghost. Unmask it.
Let's rescue father!
Yes!
You're hopelessly outnumbered.
l'll save you!
Swords are too dangerous!
Let's use our fists.
l told you that swords are
too dangerous!
Father!
Get out of here. Don't worry
about me!
Don't worry about me! Rescue father!
The monster is here!
Abracadabra! Hocus pocus!
Abraoadabra! Hocus pocus!
Windy! Windy!
Possessed by evil spirits?!
Sister!
What happened to Windy?
She's been possessed by
evil spirits.
What should we do?
Still a lot of soldiers
around. Better get inside.
Don't move!
Press down on her!
Sister!
Think of a way to save
my sister.
She's possessed by the evil spirits.
She could turn into a giant
monster at any moment.
lt's your fault, you traitor.
l'll kill you!
Wait! His troops are still out there.
We must keep him as a hostage.
She's turning into a corpse
monster!
Sister!
We must kill her immediately
Otherwise she'll turn into a monster.
You can't kill her!
Are you a good person or evil?
You won't kill Hu, but
you'll kill my sister.
Kill Hu!
No matter how many you kill here,
you still won't save the kingdom.
The emperor has no idea of
the suffering of his people.
Take my head to the emperor.
Maybe it will move him.
He'll be convinced of our
sincerity and loyalty.
Father, if you die we'll
have no one to lead us.
Take my head instead.
No! Take our heads.
Bastards! What good is it to
cut off your heads?
Who are you, ordering people
about?!
l am the learned and
brilliant Elder Chu!
The learned and brilliant
Elder Chu.
Please guide us.
None of you are permitted to die.
Please explain!
Explain?!
Your severed heads will mean
nothing to the emperor.
You'll have died in vain.
Need l explain more?
Stupid pigs!
What about her?
To exorcise her, she needs
a dose of ''yang'' energy.
l am not powerful enough.
We better do something soon
or it will be too late.
What can we do?
Try this magic charm. lt may
or may not work.
Hurry up and pull Miss Windy down.
OK.
l order the evil spirits to
be exercised.
How did this happen?
l've forced the evil spirit from her.
lf she gets a quick dose of ''yang''
energy, there will be a gleam of hope.
Hurry up.
Hurry!
l'm a monk. l must not get
too close to women.
Don't be afraid of her ugliness.
How do we give her ''yang'' energy?
With your mouth, of course.
Mouth?
What then? Your ears?
Send me to her.
Abracadabra! Hocus pocus!
Sister!
A real man is afraid of nothing.
Lord, a golden-robed priest
is on his way here.
A golden-robed priest?
Put your swords down!
Not enough! More!
Lower your swords!
Put all your swords down!
There are evildoers behind
every country's downfall.
Take my head and collect
your reward.
The way that you look death
calmly in the face,
proves that you are loyal to
our country.
Even though our political
views are different,
l'm still willing to help you.
The golden-robed Taoist
outside is the High Priest.
The High Priest?
All the rites and rituals in
the palace...
the emperor consults him
for guidance.
lf he speaks on your behalf,
justice will triumph.
Father!
Lord Fu, if you trust me,
let me go to him.
l'll explain the true situation.
Father, he might betray you!
He could have killed me had
he wanted to.
Still not awake?!
Enough! l'm going to puke.
Elder!
l am here to pay my respects
to the high priest.
Lord Fu is not a traitor.
He is a loyal subject, a patriot.
l hope that you will uphold justice.
There are many who cannot
tell between good and evil.
They do not know the
hardships of the imperial court.
The purpose of my journey
is to pacify the people.
l'll intercede at court on
behalf of these loyal subjects.
Amen! Amen!
Thank you, High Priest!
How are you, Autumn?
Women are very tempting.
lf l didn't exercise self-control...
my energy would have been dissipated.
Hu is treacherous and disrupts
the High Priest's harmony.
Please stay here.
The convict Lord Fu is here
to see the High Priest.
l pay my respects to the High Priest.
Amen! Amen! You have a
murderous air about you.
Put down your weapons.
l've been framed, but l am
concerned about our nation.
You're so merciful.Guide the
emperor to save the nation.
Life is chaotic.
Mistakes can always be corrected.
ln my former life l was evil
so l must do good in this life.
Release my soul from purgatory.
Evil chanting?!
Don't be tricked!
Sit down!
His mercy is false! Don't be
tricked by his devilish voice!
Abracadabra! Freeze!
l order the evil spirits to
be exercised!
l am the absoulute Buddha.
What kind of evil spirit
are you!
Even before Buddha you
refuse to reveal your true appearance!
The spirit of evil?!
l am what l look like!
l don't believe you are Buddha!
Let's go over and see if
you're real or false.
Don't!
Abracadabra! Hocus pocus!
Elder!
The bastard Hu betrayed us.
l'll take care of things here.
Leave quickly!
Abracadabra! Hocus pocus!
The universe revolves.
May Buddha be in your heart.
l knew he was false,
but couldn't conquer him.
l failed!
l can't perform my magic
with you here.
l'll open a tunnel in the
earth for you. Hurry!
Autumn!
Hurry up!
l can't hold out.
Hurry!
Abracadabra! Hurry!
Father!
They've escaped for now but
l'll get them in the end.
Guard the three we've captured!
Yes!
What about Lord Fu?
They have admitted their errors.
They have departed.
People should acknowledge
the immensity of the universe.
l just heard a fight going on.
Your ears aren't clean!
Vacate your mind to attain
perfect peace of mind.
l'm very cold.
Sian!
Don't leave me!
Don't be reincarnated so soon.
lt's too hard to be mortal now.
You're so good to Sian.
l never realized how much
you missed her!
Frost fills the sky over
10 Mile Lake.
Silken threads anxoius of youth.
Looking at the moon and
feeling lonely.
Envious of lovers, not of
immortality.
Sian!
Sian, what are you doing here?
Hide! You can't let the sun
shine on you!
lf the sun shines on you,
your soul will be scattered.
You would never be reincarnated!
Why don't you listen to me? Sian!
Oh, it's you! l'm sorry.
Once again l've made a mistake.
l mistook you for she.
So there really is someone
named Sian!
ls she the one in the painting?
Do you miss her very much?
She's already dead and buried.
We'll never meet again.
lf you want, you can
call me Sian for now.
For now?
l understand.
You're betrothed to another.
When l knew Sian,
she was also betrothed to
somebody else.
lt's beyond my control.
Sian said exactly the same thing.
You are morial; she's a ghost
But you're both exactly the same.
Are we very much alike?
Too much so.
You gave me false hope.
Anyway, false hope is
better than none.
Excuse me!
Here's your tea.
Your meal will be served presently.
Please make yourselves at home.
l've seen that man before. He's...
The tea is poisoned!
This inn is run by thieves!
Really!
ls the water boiling?
The blade sharpened?
Everything's ready.
Put the man in the cauldron
immediately.
Save the woman for tonight,
to warm our cold beds.
Kill!
Slice them up good!
Right on!
Stop!
Watch where you're stabbing!
They escaped through the window.
lt's dangerous here.
This is no way to escape!
Better jump into the tree and hide.
l still haven't recovered.
No energy to jump.
Don't worry about me. Run!
No, l won't leave you.
This time there's no escape!
l never thought we'd die here.
Elder, it's our fault for
getting you involved.
l'm not Elder Chu.
l'm just a poor scholar.
No matter who you are...
l feel fortunate to die
with the one l love.
We'll never be parted again.
Hold me!
Let me be on the outside so
that the wolf eats me first.
You're wonderful.
So are you.
lf we could be like this
forever, it would be great.
Orchid Monastery!
What's the Orchid Monastery?
How could l have forgotten
about Yan?
Who is he?
The bearded man in the Orchid
Monastery. A wizard in the occult.
lf we find him, we can deal
with the High Priest.
lsn't the High Priest
returning to the capital city?
Why go to his palace?
He needs a tranquil place
to meditate.
Only holy people may enter
this sacred place. Stay where you are.
This is the hour of the eclipse.
My body is changing against
my wish.
Why are all the officials of
the imperial court here?
Lord Chiang! Lord Yang! Lord Lee!
l was escorting Lord Fu back
to the capital...
But couldn't complete my
mission. Allow me to explain
Lord Chiang!
A hollow shell?
Lord Yang is a hollow shell, too?
What kind of a place is this?
Are you demons?
What did you do with the
flesh and blood of these officials?
You demons, come out and
face me!
Why did you do with the flesh and
blood of these officials?
What evil intentions do you
harbour?
Are they all hollow shells?!
l'm going to destroy all of
you evil monks.
Strange, where have they hidden?
Autumn? Moon? Lord Fu?
Lord Fu!
What happened?
Where are the others?
l was wrong to believe you!
You've caused so much harm!
What other plots do you have
up your sleave?
We were tricked.
The High Priest is a demon!
He turned many officials
into walking corpses.
We must report this to the emperor.
Otherwise, the kingdom will
be beyond redemption.
Oh, he's the one who
instigated this calamity!
No wonder the court is in
upheaval.
We must hurry to rescue the others.
We can talk later.
Moon!
Autumn!
There are demons in the court, so l must
get involved in affairs of state
Everyone must do his bit.
Hurry! There's danger everywhere.
Let's get past this hurdle first.
These demonic monks have
great magical powers.
Once he's awake we won't be
able to escape, so hurry!
Autumn, get out of here!
Don't fight anymore!
This is a scene of desolation.
Lord, ride my horse.
More chanting!
l'll use my powers to
help you concentrate.
Come back, Hu.
You'll never beat him.
Put down your butchers' knives.
Bow before Buddha!
Hu, don't sacrifice yourself in vain!
l mistakenly trusted these demons
and slaughtered righteous officials.
To atone for my sins,
l'll fight him to the death.
Don't!
l'm headed for hell anyway.
Hu!
Yan, why does the wind
suddenly blow so violently?
lt's hard to tell which
direction is which.
Yan, what should we do?
Evil spirits pervade this road.
Our lives hang by a clender thread.
We mustn't stop. Follow me!
Oh, boundless heaven and earth!
Help me!
Recite the scriptures with
me! Prajna paramita...
Prajna paramita...
The Diamond Sutra incantation?
lgnoramus, behaving so
boorishly in front of me!
Prajna paramite...
Ning, Windy...get out of the way!
Oh, boundless heaven and earth.
Help me!
Buddha is present!
lf you dare to impersonate Buddha,
what would you not dare to do?
You think you can hoodwink
the people forever?
l'm going to let everyone
know what you really are!
The masses love to worship
their idols.
Why set yourself against the people?
lt's their ignorance that
has allowed you to succeed.
l'll never let them worship
demons like you.
You'll never decieve the
people again!
lf you refuse to follow my
shining beacon...
you will be destroyed!
What crap! Look out!
Justine for all!
Swords are part of the infinite!
We've only destroyed the
false cuter body.
He can come back &
attack us at any time.
We must use our swords
to fight back!
Let me introduce myself.
l'm from the Kunlun sect...
At a time like this,
let's not separate into sects.
We're all fighting the same enemy.
Destroy this demon!
Chant with me!
Prajna paramita...
The old demon has stolen into the earth
and broken through our ring of swords.
What should we do?
Watch!
What kind of demon?
Come with me!
Hold on to me as l fly.
Ning!
You pulled my sleave off.
What are you coming back for
What happened?
Gone?
Be careful!
Moon, look after your father
l'll help Yan.
Autumn, be careful!
The demon's actually a
giant centipede!
That worm can never be a dragon.
Elder!
l've never had to deal with
such a giant creature.
What should we do now?
Pierce the crown of its head
Ning!
Windy!
The flying sword!
Prajna paramita!
Exercise the demons!
Oh, boundless heaven and
earth. Help me!
Elder!
Autumn!
Two heads are better than one.
Abracadabra. Hocus pocus.
Hocus pocus.
l've been in the Orchid
Monastery for so long...
l didn't know the world was
so full of devils and demons
lt's hard to separate the
living from the dead.
The world is in chaos.
lt's a good thing you hid in
the Orchid Monastery.
Otherwise l might never
have found you.
We share the same ideals...
We should roam this world together
and fight for justice.
We should work together.
What are you saying?
l've always led a solitary existence.
Last time, l almost died
trying to help you save Sian
This time, l've helped you
battle the demons...
and almost lost my life.
lt's better if we go our own ways.
When you need my help,
l'll return and save you.
Be careful, Autumn!
We're locked in. We must
think of a way to escape.
You're right! l've really
caused you harm.
Our bodies are restrained. We can be
saved only if our souls can escape.
Souls?
Will we have enough energy
to later let the souls back in?
This is the only way!
Chant along with me.
The spirit of Buddha conquers all!
Goodness is indestructible.
Oh, boundless heaven and earth.
Help me!
Hocus pocus!
Autumn!
Yan!
Soul, return!
My soul can't return to my body!
Autumn, catch the soul!
His power isn't strong enough.
l'll help him.
Prajna paramita...
l can't catch it.
Moon!
What's all the hubub outside
What hubbub? l don't hear
anything!
Who's getting married?
Such a large golden pig!
lt's a gift to Lord Fu from
the emperor.
Since he exposed the
traitors in the imperial
court, he performed a great
service for the emperor.
lt's a wedding gift for Lord
Fu's daughter.
Moon!
Ning!
ls Windy getting...
Sister is already married.
Don't cause her any trouble.
l'm about to start on a journey.
Give her my best wishes for
a happy marriage.
l will. Take care of yourself.
Adieu!
lt's hard to differentiate
between true and false hopes
Now l understand why you
stay away from our mortal world.
Mortals are forgetful.
Good deeds fade like the wind.
No matter what you've done,
it's soon forgotten.
ls forgetting good or bad?
Should we have hopes?
You said you'd cherish no
hopes!
Sister, don't hesitate!
Go to him!
Windy?!
Ning!
Let's go, hurry!
You go back.
Farewell!
Take care!
Let's go!
The path of life
Are dreams, like the length of the path
The storm on the way
Pass by as you go along
ln the world
How many ways can one dream?
Looking for dream-like love
And the path goes on
Life is what
Dreams and desires are made of
Somewhere in the dream
There are traces of tears
Where to go to?
To find where my heart wants to go
The wind seems to sign in the dream,
and the path and l go on.
The path of living
The happiness of youth
The path is full of difficulties
That no light can be seen
ln the dust,
how many ways can one find happiness
The wind and rain pass like a dream,
and the path goes on.